<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android 6 &amp; 7 Samples</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="testing_doze_app_standby"><![CDATA[Doze and App Standby are enabled for all apps running on Marshmallow (or later) devices, which means your app needs to know how to handle Doze and App Standby modes. Most apps should be fine, but some (especially apps utilizing the AlarmManager) will need to be updated in order to continue working properly.<br /><br />In order to ensure your app will work with Doze, it should be tested ahead of time. You should ensure your app recovers gracefully from Doze or App Standby. In particular, with App Standby, you want to check if notifications and background jobs continue to function properly. <br /><br />You can use the Android Debug Bridge (adb) to force the system to cycle through Doze or App Standby modes using the following commands.<br /><br />Doze:<pre><br />adb shell dumpsys battery unplug<br />adb shell dumpsys deviceidle step<br />//Second command may need to be run multiple times. You want the device state to be <i>\'idle\'</i>.</pre><br /><br />App Standby:<br /><pre>//Force the app into App Standby mode<br />adb shell dumpsys battery unplug<br />adb shell am set-inactive <packageName> true<br /><br />//Wake up your app<br />adb shell am set-inactive <packageName> false<br />adb shell am get-inactive <packageName><br /></pre>]]></string>
    <string name="auto_backup_info"><![CDATA[For all devices running Android 6.0 (or higher), backups are automatically enabled.  Files are backed up to Google Drive (max of 25MB, not counting against a user\'s space).<br /><br />To exclude all files, the following line can be added to your AndroidManifest.xml\'s application tag:<br /><i>android:allowBackup="false"</i><br /><br />An XML file can be created to specify which specific files should be included or excluded.  An example of this can be found in the source code for this app.]]></string>
    <string name="app_linking_info"><![CDATA[Instead of always opening the app selection menu when opening a URL, starting with Android 6.0, you can configure certain URLs to be opened by your app by default.<br /><br />This is a two-step process, as you need to have confirmation both on the web domain as well as in the app.  In the app, you simply can add an <i>intent-filter</i> to your activity in AndroidManifest.xml.  An example of this can be found in this app\'s AndroidManfiest.xml<br /><br />The second piece is to add a JSON file at <i>https://domain[:optional_port]/.well-known/assetlinks.json</i><br />This JSON file will look something like this:</br><font size="10sp"><br />[{<br />\u0009"relation": ["delegate_permission/common.handle_all_urls"],<br />\u0009"target": {<br />\u0009\u0009"namespace": "android_app",<br />\u0009\u0009"package_name": "org.faziodev.android67samples",<br />\u0009\u0009"sha256_cert_fingerprints":<br />\u0009\u0009["14:6D:E9:83:C5:73:06:50:D8:EE:B9:95:2F:34:FC:64:16:A0:83:42:E6:1D:BE:A8:8A:04:96:B2:3F:CF:44:E5"]<br />\u0009}</font><br />}]<br />]]></string>
    <string name="data_saver_description">Data Saver allows users to limit the amount of data that is being used by their device when they\'re on a metered connection.  In the code, you\'re able to determine if the device is on a metered connection and what the Data Saver settings for your app will be. (Enabled, Disabled, or Whitelisted)</string>
    <string name="data_saver_status">"Background data is %1$s"</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_tile_api_header">Quick Settings Tile API</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_tile_api_description">Quick Setting Tiles are located in the notification shade and are meant to complete urgently required or frequently used tasks.\n\nThis includes things like turning on/off a flashlight/WiFi/Do Not Disturb or showing someone their battery level.\n\nIt should not be used for shortcuts to launch an app. We already have those, they\'re called shortcuts, and they live in the App Drawer or on pages.</string>
    <string name="metered_connection_status_default">Metered connection status is unknown.</string>
    <string name="restrict_background_status_default">Restrict background status is unknown.</string>
    <string name="refresh_button">Refresh</string>
    <string name="multi_window_description"><![CDATA[Android now (natively) will handle multi-window, both side-by-side and top + bottom.  ]]></string>

</resources>
